dataquest.io 2019-09-16

# Privacy Policy – Dataquest

Last updated: June 13, 2019

Dataquest Labs, Inc. (the “Company” “us”, “we”, or “our”) respects your privacy and is committed to protecting it through our compliance with this Privacy Policy. This Privacy Policy is part of our Terms of Use [ _available here_](https://www.dataquest.io/terms) _._ We operate the [_https://www.dataquest.io_](https://www.dataquest.io/) website (the "Service").

This page informs you of our policies regarding the collection, use, and disclosure of Personal Information when you use our Service.

We will not use or share your information with anyone except as described in this Privacy Policy.

We use your Personal Information for providing and improving the Service. By using the Service, you agree to the collection and use of information in accordance with this Privacy Policy. Unless otherwise defined in this Privacy Policy, terms used in this Privacy Policy have the same meanings as in our Terms of Use, accessible at [_https://www.dataquest.io/terms_](https://www.dataquest.io/terms).

Please read this Privacy Policy carefully to understand our policies and practices regarding your information and how we will treat it, as you agree to this Privacy Policy by using the Service.  **If you do not agree with our policies and practices, do not use the Service.**

## Children's Privacy

Only persons age 18 or older have permission to access our Service. Our Service is not intended for anyone under the age of 13 years old.

We do not knowingly collect personally identifiable information from children under 13. If we become aware that we have collected Personal Information from a child under age 13 without verification of parental consent, we take steps to remove that information from our servers. If you believe we might have any information from or about a child under 13, or that there may be a user under the age of 13, please contact us immediately at legal@dataquest.io.

If you are based in the European Economic Area (“EEA”) you may only use the Service if you are over the age at which you can provide consent to data processing under the laws of your country or if verifiable parental consent for your use of the Service  has been provided to us. 

## Information Collection

We collect several types of information from and about users of the Service, including information:

  * by which you may be personally identified, such as name, phone number, and e-mail address, billing information, billing address (“Personal Information”);
  * that is ascertained through our use of third-party applications, including but not limited to your user behavior and trends;
  * that is about you but individually does not identify you, such as the city where you live;
  * by way of surveys where you may supply us information, such as, but not limited to, gender, age, or income level; and/or
  * about your internet connection, the equipment you use to access the Service, and usage details.

We collect information from you in two ways:

  * Directly from you when you provide it to us.
  * Automatically as you navigate through the site. Information collected automatically may include usage details, IP addresses, web browser preferences, and information collected through cookies and other tracking technologies. Although we do not correlate tracking information to individuals, some information collected, such as IP addresses, will be unique.

## Log Data

We collect information that your browser sends whenever you visit our Service ("Log Data"). This Log Data may include information such as your computer's Internet Protocol ("IP") address, browser type, browser version, the pages of our Service that you visit, the time and date of your visit, the time spent on those pages and other statistics.

In addition, we may use third party services such as Google Analytics that collect, monitor and analyze this type of information in order to increase our Service's functionality. These third party service providers have their own privacy policies addressing how they use such information.

## Do Not Track Settings

Please note that the Service does not support “Do Not Track” browser settings and does not currently participate in any “Do Not Track” frameworks that would allow us to respond to signals or other mechanisms from you regarding the collection (or not) of your personal or non-personally identifiable information.

## Cookies

Cookies are files with a small amount of data, which may include an anonymous unique identifier. Cookies are sent to your browser from a web site and transferred to your device. We use cookies to collect information in order to improve our services for you.

You can instruct your browser to refuse all cookies or to indicate when a cookie is being sent. The Help feature on most browsers provide information on how to accept cookies, disable cookies or to notify you when receiving a new cookie.

If you do not accept cookies, you may not be able to use some features of our Service and we recommend that you leave them turned on.

## Disclosure of Your Information ** **

We may employ third party companies and individuals to facilitate our Service, to provide the Service on our behalf, to perform Service-related services and/or to assist us in analyzing how our Service is used. These third parties have access to your Personal Information only to perform specific tasks on our behalf and are obligated not to disclose or use your information for any other purpose.

We may disclose aggregated information about our users, and information that does not identify any individual, without restriction.

We may disclose personal information that we collect or you provide:

  * To our subsidiaries and affiliates.
  * To contractors, service providers, and other third parties we use to support our business.
  * To a buyer or other successor in the event of a merger, divestiture, restructuring, reorganization, dissolution, or other sale or transfer of some or all of the Company’s assets whether as a going concern or as part of bankruptcy, liquidation, or similar proceeding, in which personal information held by the Company about the Service’s users is among the assets transferred.
  * For any other purpose disclosed by us when you provide the information.
  * To comply with any court order, law, or legal process, including to respond to any government or regulatory request.
  * If we believe disclosure is necessary or appropriate to protect the rights, property, or safety of the Company, our customers, or others.

## Data Retention

We retain personal information we collect from you where we have an ongoing legitimate business need to do so (for example, to provide you with a service you have requested or to comply with applicable legal, tax, or accounting requirements).

When we have no ongoing legitimate business need to process your personal information, we will either delete or anonymize it or, if this is not possible (for example, because your personal information has been stored in backup archives), then we will securely store your personal information and isolate it from any further processing until deletion is possible.

## Choices About How We Use and Disclose Your Information

We strive to provide you with choices regarding the personal information you provide to us. We have created mechanisms to provide you with the following control over your information:

  *  **Tracking Technologies and Advertising.** You can set your browser to refuse all or some browser cookies, or to alert you when cookies are being sent. To learn how you can manage your Flash cookie settings, visit the Flash player settings page on Adobe's [_website_](http://www.macromedia.com/support/documentation/en/flashplayer/help/settings_manager07.html). If you disable or refuse cookies, please note that some parts of this site may then be inaccessible or not function properly.
  *  **Promotional Offers from the Company.** If you do not wish to have your contact information used by the Company to promote our own or third parties' products or services, you can opt-out by sending us an email stating your request to [_legal@dataquest.io_](mailto:legal@dataquest.io). If we have sent you a promotional email, you may send us a return email asking to be omitted from future email distributions. This opt out does not apply to information provided to the Company as a result of a registration, product service experience or other transactions.

We do not control third parties' collection or use of your information to serve interest-based advertising. However these third parties may provide you with ways to choose not to have your information collected or used in this way. You can opt out of receiving targeted ads from members of the Network Advertising Initiative ("NAI") on the NAI's [_website_](http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp).

## Accessing and Correcting Your Information ** **

You can review and change your personal information by logging into the Service and visiting your account profile page. You may also send us an email at [_legal@dataquest.io_](mailto:legal@dataquest.io)to request access to, correct, or delete any personal information that you have provided to us. We may not accommodate a request to change information if we believe the change would violate any law or legal requirement or cause the information to be incorrect.

## Your California Privacy Rights

California Civil Code Section § 1798.83 permits users of the Service that are California residents to request certain information regarding our disclosure of personal information to third parties for their direct marketing purposes. To make such a request, please send an email to [_legal@dataquest.io_](mailto:legal@dataquest.io).

If you are a California resident, California law may provide you with additional rights regarding our use of your personal information. To learn more about your California privacy rights, visit [_CCPA Privacy Notice for California Residents_](https://leginfo.legislature.ca.gov/faces/billTextClient.xhtml?bill_id=201720180AB375).    

## European Economic Area (EEA) Users

If you are in the EEA, you have options in relation to the information and data that we have about you.  To exercise any of the options discussed below, please contact us at legal@dataquest.io. If you’re an EEA users, you may:

  * Access the information we have about you. We will make an effort to share this information with you within a reasonable time.
  * Have your information corrected or deleted. 
  * Object to us processing your information. You can ask us to stop using your information, including when we use your information to send you marketing emails or push notifications. We only send you marketing material if you've agreed to it, but if you'd rather we don't, you can easily unsubscribe at any time.
  * Withdraw your consent for us to collect and process your personal information at any time.  Withdrawing your consent will not affect the lawfulness of any processing we conducted prior to your withdrawal, nor will it affect the processing of your personal information conducted in reliance on lawful processing grounds other than consent.
  * Have the information you provided to us sent to another organization, where we hold this information with your consent or for the performance of a contract with you, where it's technically feasible.
  * Complain to a regulator. If you're based in the EEA and think that we haven't complied with data protection laws, you have a right to lodge a complaint with the [ _Data Protection Commission  in Ireland_](https://dataprotection.ie/) or with your local supervisory authority.

We respond to all requests we receive from individuals wishing to exercise their data protection rights in accordance with applicable data protection laws.

## Security

The security of your Personal Information is important to us, and we strive to implement and maintain reasonable, commercially acceptable security procedures and practices appropriate to the nature of the information we store, in order to protect it from unauthorized access, destruction, use, modification, or disclosure.

However, please be aware that no method of transmission over the internet, or method of electronic storage, is 100% secure and we are unable to guarantee the absolute security of the Personal Information we have collected from you.

Dataquest remains committed to protecting your personal information and the information you share with us in your account, including your credit card data and contact data, using reasonably available means. This includes:

  1. Investigating all employees with a thorough screening process before hire;
  2. Having employees and contractors sign a confidentiality agreement agreeing to keep all information stored by the Company confidential; and
  3. Storing all information on secure servers maintained and managed by our credit card processors and hosting providers.

## International Transfer

Your information, including Personal Information, may be transferred to — and maintained on — computers located outside of your state, province, country or other governmental jurisdiction where the data protection laws may differ than those from your jurisdiction.

If you are located outside the United States and choose to provide information to us, please note that we transfer the information, including Personal Information, to the United States and process it there.

Your consent to this Privacy Policy followed by your submission of such information represents your agreement to that transfer.

## Links To Other Sites

Our Service may contain links to other sites that are not operated by us. If you click on a third party link, you will be directed to that third party's site. We strongly advise you to review the Privacy Policy of every site you visit.

We have no control over, and assume no responsibility for the content, privacy policies or practices of any third party sites or services.

## Changes To This Privacy Policy

This Privacy Policy is effective as of June 13, 2019, and will remain in effect except with respect to any changes in its provisions in the future, which will be in effect immediately after being posted on this page.

We reserve the right to update or change our Privacy Policy at any time and you should check this Privacy Policy periodically. Your continued use of the Service after we post any modifications to the Privacy Policy on this page will constitute your acknowledgment of the modifications and your consent to abide and be bound by the modified Privacy Policy.

If we make any material changes to this Privacy Policy, we will notify you by placing a notice in the footer of our website

## Contact Us

If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, please contact us at legal@dataquest.io.
